<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NPCs on</title><link>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/tags/NPCs/</link><description>Recent content in NPCs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/tags/NPCs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Davil Starsong (Deceased)</title><link>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/NPCs/Davil-Starsong-Deceased/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/NPCs/Davil-Starsong-Deceased/</guid><description>Summary Master of Opportunities and Negotiations of the Zhentarim Founding member of the Doom Raiders Sun Elf Rogue with an affinity for magic Does most of his business in the taproom of the Yawning Portal</description></item><item><title>Durnan</title><link>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/NPCs/Durnan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/NPCs/Durnan/</guid><description>Owner and proprietor of the Yawning Portal Known Closed Lord of Waterdeep Middle Aged man who despite looking tired and haggard still has a sharp mind and a sharper sword - Grimvault Background Durnan is the owner and proprietor of the Yawning Portal.</description></item><item><title>Istrid Horn</title><link>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/Istrid-Horn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/Istrid-Horn/</guid><description>Summary Master of Trade and Coin of the Zhentarim Operates an illegal lending operation out of a heavily guarded warehouse in the Dock Ward Founding member of the Doom Raiders Open to working with the party Party Notes Test Test</description></item><item><title>Manshoon</title><link>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/Manshoon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/Manshoon/</guid><description>Summary An archwizard who hired the Doom Raiders&amp;rsquo; mercenary group The Black Network in order to found the Zhentarim
Like many wizards pushing the boundaries of magical experiments, Manshoon eventually ran in the very non-magical problem of resources.</description></item><item><title>Renear</title><link>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/Renear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/Renear/</guid><description>Member of the The Trollskull Team Father was the Open Lord Dagult Neverember, Open Lord before Larael Silverhand. Dagult embezzled a treasure of a million gold pieces and encoded it&amp;rsquo;s location in the Stone of Golorr</description></item><item><title>Skeemo Weirdbottle</title><link>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/NPCs/Skeemo-Weirdbottle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/NPCs/Skeemo-Weirdbottle/</guid><description>Summary Skeemo became the Master of Magic for the Zhentarim, setting up a cover in the Trades Ward in the form of a cramped little shop called Weirdbottle’s Concoctions.</description></item><item><title>Ziraj the Hunter</title><link>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/Ziraj-the-Hunter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bradhaas.github.io/TheCompendium/Ziraj-the-Hunter/</guid><description>Summary A burly half orc paladin and one of the original members of the Doom Raiders Loyal to anyone who shows him kindness Good Friends with Chad Background Race: Half Orc Faction: Doom Raiders Abilities: Arrow Paladin Party Relationship Party fled from Ziraj&amp;rsquo;s huge arrow bolts through the city as they fled Gralhund Villa with the Stone of Golorr Chad and Ziraj struck up a friendship</description></item></channel></rss>